A Guide to the Richmond Jaycees, 1936-2002
Library of Virginia
- Project Files, 1956-2002.
  - Major League Baseball Scout, 1976-1977. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Management Development Programming, 1984-1985. (Box 83, Folder 6-10)
  - Management Development Programming, 1985-1986. (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
  - Management Development Programming, 1985-1986. (Box 85, Folder 1-5)
  - Management Development Programming, 1987-1988. (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - Management Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 86, Folder 3-5)
  - Management Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Management Development Programming, 1991-1992. (Box 87, Folder 2-5)
  - Management Development Programming, 1991-1992. (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Management Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 88, Folder 3-5)
  - Management Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 89, Folder 1-5)
  - Management Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 90, Folder 1-6)
  - Management Development Programming, 1993-1994. (Box 91, Folder 1-5)
  - Management Development Programming, 1993-1994. (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - March of Dimes Walk-A-Thon, 1985. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - March of Dimes Walk-A-Thon, 1986. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - March of Dimes Walk-A-Thon, 1986. (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Mayor's Report, 1964. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Media Night, 1992. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Membership, 1992-1993. (Box 92, Folder 6-7)
  - Membership Brochure, 1992. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Membership Development Programming, 1989-1990. (Box 92, Folder 9-10)
  - Membership Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Membership Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
  - Membership Development Programming, 1991-1992. (Box 93, Folder 4-7)
  - Membership Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
  - Membership Meetings, 1993-1994. (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Membership Open House, 1992-1993. (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Membership Placement, 1967. (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Membership Recruitment, 1967-1968. (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Membership Retention, 1967-1968. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Membership Social, 1990. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Membership Social (December), 1990. (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Membership Social (February), 1991. (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Membership Social (March), 1991. (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Membership Social (Capital Club), 1990-1991. (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Membership Socials (M-Nights), 1989-1990. (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
  - Membership Socials, 1990-1991. (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Membership Socials, 1990. (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Membership Social, 1990-1991. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Membership Survey, 1990. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Membership Survey, 1992-1993. (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Membership Survey, 1993-1994. (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Membership Survey, 1993-1994. (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Men's Jaycee Softball Team, 1990. (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Mental Health Study Group, 1964. (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - MET NET in Omaha, 1992-1993. (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Metro Consumer Education, 1975-1976. (Box 96, Folder 1-2)
  - Metropolitan Affairs Seminar, 1964-1965. (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Mid Year Board Retreat, 1992-1993. (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Mississauga Twinning, 1978. (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Mixed Beverage Referendum, 1968. (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Model General Assembly, 1985. (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Model General Assembly, 1986. (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Model General Assembly, 1987. (Box 97, Folder 1-3)
  - Model General Assembly, 1987-1988. (Box 97, Folder 4-5)
  - Model General Assembly, 1990-1991. (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
  - Model General Assembly, 1992. (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Model General Assembly, 1993. (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Model General Assembly, 1993. (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Monticello Candlelight Tour, 1992. (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Movie Afternoon, 1989. (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - National Meetings, 1964-1969. (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - National Tobacco Festival Float, 1980. (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - New Board Training, 1992-1993. (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - New Member Orientation, 1967-1968. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - New Member Orientations, 1988-1989. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - New Member Orientations, 1989-1990. (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - New Member Orientations, 1991-1992. (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - New Member Orientations, 1991-1992. (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - New Membership, 1991-1992. (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - New Virginians Concert, 1976. (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - New Election Services, 1976. (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Night at the Theater, 1968. (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - 19th Annual XL 102 Chili Cook-Off, ca. 2002. (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - 90-60-30 Countdown to Renewing, 1990-1991. (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - 90-60-30 Countdown to Joining, 1990-1991. (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - No-Fault Insurance Forum, 1972. (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Nominations and Elections, 1972-1973. (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Nominations and Elections, 1984. (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Nominations and Elections, 1984. (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Nominations and Elections, 1992. (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Nominations and Elections, 1992. (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Hugh O'Brian Youth Seminar, 1977-1978. (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Open Houses, 1991-1992. (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Open Houses, 1991-1992. (Box 101, Folder 2-3)
  - Operation Identification, 1972. (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Operation Identification, 1973. (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Operation Identification, 1975. (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Operation Identification, 1978-1979. (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Orientation, 1987-1988. (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Orientation Meeting, 2002. (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Outing for Underprivileged Children, 1959. (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Outing for Underprivileged Children, 1970. (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Outing for Underprivileged Children, 1967. (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Outing for Underprivileged Children, 1968. (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Outing for Underprivileged Children, 1970. (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Outing for Underprivileged Children, 1972. (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Outstanding Young Citizen, 1987-1988. (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Outstanding Young Citizen, 1991. (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Outstanding Young Educator, 1968. (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Outstanding Young Farmer, 1964-1965. (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Outstanding Young Farmer, 1965-1966. (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Outstanding Young Farmer, 1966-1967. (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Oyster Roast and Pig Pickin', 1991. (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Oyster Roast and Pig Pickin', 1991. (Box 102, Folder 10-11)
  - Painting Party, 1986. (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Paperbacks for Prisoners, 1987. (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Parade of Chapters, 1988-1989. (Box 103, Folder 3-4)
  - Parade of Chapters, 1989. (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Pari-Mutual Betting Forum, 1971-1972. (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Parliamentary Procedure Class, 1967-1968. (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - The Party, 1990-1991. (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - The Party, 1992. (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - The Party, 1992. (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Party Bus to Camp Virginia Jaycee, 1991. (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Party Bus to Camp Virginia Jaycee, 1991. (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Party Bus to Camp Virginia Jaycee, 1992. (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Party Cruise on the Annabel Lee, 1991-1992. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Party for Autistic Children, 1987. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Peaks and Otter Camping Trip, 1987. (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Sidney D. Peck Award Nomination, 1984-1985. (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Personal Goal Setting and Stress Management, 1989-1990. (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Personal Success Seminar, 1992-1993. (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Phenylketonuria and Reflectorized License Plate Resolutions, 1996. (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Phillip's Pitch, Hit, and Throw, 1970. (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Physical Fitness Leadership Award, 1965. (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Physical Fitness Seminar, 1974. (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Pitch in Richmond, 1972-1973. (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Plan of the Year, 1989. (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Plan of the Year, 1990-1991. (Box 104, Folder 15-16)
  - Plan of the Year, 1990-1991. (Box 105, Folder 1-4)
  - Plan of the Year, 1990-1991.
  - Plan of the Year, 1991-1992. (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Plan of the Year, 1991-1992. (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Plan of the Year, 1992-1993. (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Planned Parenthood, 2002. (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Police Auxiliary, 1974-1977. (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Police Auxiliary Study Committee, 1974-1975. (Box 106, Folder 5-7)
  - Police Auxiliary Study Committee, 1974-1975. (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Police Night, 1968. (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Police Reserve Study and Formation Committee,. (Box 107, Folder 3-7)
  - Police Reserve Study and Formation Committee, 1976-1977. (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Police Ride Along, 1970. (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Police Ride Along, 1971. (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Police Ride Along, 1978. (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Politics, 1964. (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Politics 1964 -- Presidential Spokesmen, 1964. (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Position Study of Proposed Richmond Coliseum, 1966-1967. (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Pre-Naturalization Classes for Future Citizens, 1964-1965. (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - President's Team Parade, 1985-1986. (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Press Night, 1972. (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Press Night, 1972. (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Press Night, 1974-1975. (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Night, 1975. (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Press Night -- Marshall Nguyen Cab By, 1975-1976. (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - "Pride in Richmond" Tee Shirt Sale, 1982. (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Prisoner Rehabilitation Program, 1967-1968. (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1987-1988. (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Program Activities, 1967-1968. (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Project Friend, 1970-1971. (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Project Play, 1992. (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Project W.A.R.M., 1990. (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Project W.A.R.M., 1990. (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Project W.A.R.M., 1991. (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Project W.A.R.M., 1991-1992. (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Project W.A.R.M, 1992-1993. (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Promotion of Poll Tax Payment, 1963. (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Promoting Richmond Bus Tour, 1966. (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Prospective Members Recruitment, 1991-1992. (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Public Forum on Mental Retardation, 1966. (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations, 1963-1964. (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations, 1964-1965. (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Public Relations, 1964-1965. (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations, 1965-1966. (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Public Relations, 1974. (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations, 1987-1988. (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
  - Public Relations, 1990-1991. (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations, 1990-1991. (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations, 1992-1993. (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Public School System Evaluation Meeting, 1964-1965. (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Publication of Handbook, 1967-1968. (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Publicity -- "New Dominion", 1964-1965. (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Pump It Up for Cystic Fibrosis Week, 1989-1990. (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Punt, Pass, and Kick, 1987. (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Race Relations, 1992-1993. (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Racquetball Tournament for Cancer, 1987. (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Racquetball Tournament for Cancer, 1988. (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Racquetball Tournament for Cancer, 1988. (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Rafting on the James, 1991. (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Rape Awareness Seminar, 1991. (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Reception Honoring Greg Thomas, President of U.S. Jaycees, 1991-1992. (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Recycle Your Attitude, 1991. (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Region III Meeting, 1976. (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Regular Program -- James C. Wheat, Speaker, 1971. (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Regular Program -- E. Bruce Heilman, Speaker, 1971.
  - Religion and Politics, 1988. (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Resolution for H.I. Willett, 1964. (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Resolution on the Proposed Citizen-Police Review Board, 1969. (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Retreat and Plan, 1990-1991. (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Rib Championship, 1989. (Box 114, Folder 11-12)
  - Richmond Braves Baseball Game, 1991. (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Braves Night, 1983. (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Bus Tour (Phase II), 1965-1966. (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Bus Tour, 1967. (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Bus Tour, 1970. (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Richmond Bus Tour, 1972-1973. (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Richmond Children's Festival, 1990. (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Richmond Housing Tour, 1970. (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Richmond Jaycee Banner, 1987. (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Richmond Marathon, 1978-1979. (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Richmond Marathon Stand, 1984. (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Richmond Marathon Stand, 1985. (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Richmond Marathon Stand, 1986. (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Richmond Marathon Stand, 1987. (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Marathon Stand, 1987. (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Special Olympics, 1989. (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Teachers' Salary Study, 1964. (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Richmond Tomorrow -- Get Involved, 1990. (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Richmond Tour Promotion, 1967-1968. (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Richmond Visitor Information Center, 1972. (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - River Rock, 1992-1993. (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Roaring Twenties Party, 1967. (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Rosy Grier Youth Shelter Trip, 1989. (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Roster/Handbook Publication, 1980. (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - RSVP Reception, 1986. (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Safe Driving Road-e-o, 1962. (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Safe Driving Road-e-o, 1964. (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Safe Driving Road-e-o, 1965. (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Safe Driving Road-e-o, 1966. (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Safe Driving Road-e-o, 1967. (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Safe Driving Road-e-o, 1969. (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Sales Tax Debate, 1965. (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Safety Through Seat Belts, 1962. (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Sale of Seat Belt and First Aid Kits, 1962. (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Salvation Army Kettle, 1962. (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Salvation Army Kettle, 1986. (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Sargent Santa, 1986. (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - School Busing Resolution, 1970. (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - School Issues Forum, 1971. (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - School Issues Questionnaire, 1971. (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Shall We Dance, 1992-1993. (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Shooters Education, 1984-1985. (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Sickle Cell Anemia Awareness, 1971-1972. (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Sign Language, 1991. (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Sister City Project, 1968-1969. (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Six Pack Training, 1991-1992. (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Six Pack Training, 1991-1992. (Box 118, Folder 1-2)
  - Skating Party for Children with Autism, 1990. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Skating Party Two, 1993-1994. (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Ski Trip, 1988. (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Smoke Alarm Project, 1977-1978. (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Smoke Alarms for the Elderly, 1985. (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Soap Box Derby, 1958-1959. (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Soap Box Derby, 1962. (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Soap Box Derby, 1984. (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Soap Box Derby, 1985. (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Soap Box Derby, 1987. (Box 119, Folder 1-5)
  - Social for the Elderly, 1991. (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Social for the Elderly, 1991. (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - South Eastern Metropolitan Affairs Seminar, 1965. (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Spark Plug Program, 1967-1968. (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Spark Plug, 1976-1979. (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Speak Up Jaycee, 1967-1968. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Speak Up, 1983-1984. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Special Olympics, 1987. (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Special Olympics, 1990. (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Special Olympics, 1991. (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Speechcraft, 1992-1993. (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - SPOKE Program, 1967-1968. (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Spokes Across the Continent, 1976. (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Spokes and Folks -- Bicycle Safety, 1977-1978. (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Sponsor Basketball Team in Southern Conference Tournament, 1961. (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Sponsor Southern Conference Basketball Conference, 1960. (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Sports Kits Abroad, 1965-1966. (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Spring Clean Up, 1979. (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Spring into Summer Membership Social, 1990. (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Spring Membership Drive, 1967. (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Spring Regional Meeting, 1980. (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1992. (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - State Candidates Night, 1971. (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - State Convention, 1964. (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - State Convention, 1967. (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - State Convention, 1967. (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - State Fair, 1973. (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - State Junior Champ Track and Field Development Program, 1966-1967. (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - State Office Candidates Night, 1969. (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - State Senatorial Candidate's Night, 1967. (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Steering Committee for Junior Jaycees, 1993. (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - "Step Ahead with Ed" -- Ed White for President, Virginia Jaycees, 1966. (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Stop Measles Campaign, 1967-1968. (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Stop Polio Sunday, 1963-1964. (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Stop Rubella Campaign, 1970. (Box 122, Folder 1-2)
  - Strawberry Hill Races, 2002. (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Street Smart, 1992-1993. (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Study of the Pre-Naturalization Course taught by Henry F. Miller, 1967-1968. (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Suit and Tie Corporate Recruiting, 1991-1992. (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Summer Encore, 1990. (Box 122, Folder 7-8)
  - Summer Encore, 1990-1991. (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Summer Encore, 1991. (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Summer Jobs for Youth, 1983. (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Summer Picnic, 1984. (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Superbowl Party, 1992-1993. (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Survey of Community Opinion on Richmond Community Renewal Program, 1966-1967. (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1956-1986. (Box 123, Folder 7-8)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1970-1976. (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1972-1973. (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1979-1980. (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1981. (Box 124, Folder 2-3)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1983-1984. (Box 124, Folder 4-5)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1988-1989. (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1990-1991. (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1990-1991. (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Swine Flu Inoculation Clinic, 1976-1977. (Box 124, Folder 9-10)
  - Take a Break, 1976-1977. (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Take a Break, 1978-1979. (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Take me Out to the Ball Game, 1992-1993. (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Tax Clinic, 1975. (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Teen Pregnancy Seminar, 1991. (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - 30-60-90 Welcome, 1991-1992. (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Time Management Seminar, 1976-1977. (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Time Management, 1987. (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - To Host the November Quarterly Work Conference, 1962. (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Tour of Reynolds Metal Plant, 1961. (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Tourist Center Proposal, 1963-1970. (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Tourist Information Center, 1972-1974. (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Safety Survey (Phase I), 1965-1966. (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Trafficways, 1966-1967. (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Travelland, 1962-1963. (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Travelland (Phase IV), 1965-1966. (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Travelland (Phase V), 1966-1967. (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Travelland, 1967-1968. (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Travelland, 1969-1971. (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Transportation for the Blind, 1975-1976. (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Treasure Hunt for Charity, 1991. (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Treasure Hunt for Charity, 1991. (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Treasure Hunt for Charity, 1991. (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Tune in the "Turned on Crisis, 1970-1971. (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - 25th Anniversary Night, 1962-1963. (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Ukrop's Golden Receipts, 1990-1991. (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Project, 1989-1990. (Box 134, Folder 1-3)
  - Uniform Traffic Signs and Ordinance Survey, 1964. (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Urban Crisis Survey, 1967-1968. (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Urban Issues Seminar, 1970. (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Urban Issues Seminar, 1971. (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Urban Issues Seminar, 1971. (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Senatorial Candidates' Night, 1966. (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Candidates' Night, 1972. (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Venereal Disease Attack Program, 1974-1975. (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Veteran's Assistance, 1971. (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - VA COOL/Project READY, 1990-1991. (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - VA COOL/Project READY, 1990-1991. (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Heroes, 1991-1992. (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Heroes, 1992-1993. (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Museum Tour, 1992. (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Legislative Reapportionment Study and Action, 1964. (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Visit the Kids, 1978-1979. (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Visitations, 1990-1991. (Box 128, Folder 1-2)
  - Visitations, 1992-1993. (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Visitations/Redline Assistance, 1991-1992. (Box 128, Folder 4-5)
  - Visitations/Redline Assistance, 1991-1992. (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Visiting Teachers from Great Britain, 1963. (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Vocational Education Directory, 1963-1964. (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Vocational-Technical Education Study, 1964-1965. (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Volleyball Tournament, 1988. (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Volleyball Tournament, 1989. (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Volunteer Day -- Central Virginia Food Bank, 2002. (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Voter Registration, 1964. (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Voter Registration, 1968. (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Voter Registration, 1972. (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Voter Registration, 1975-1976. (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Voter Registration, 1976. (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Voter Registration, 1985. (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Voter Registration, 1986. (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Voter Registration, 1989. (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Washington D.C. Trip for Youth, 1993. (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Ways and Means, 1959-1960. (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Ways and Means, 1960-1961. (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Ways and Means, 1961-1962. (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, 1963-1964. (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, 1964-1965. (Box 130, Folder 3-4)
  - Ways and Means, 1966-1967. (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, 1966-1967. (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, 1967-1968. (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, 1969-1970. (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - We're on a Roll, 1992-1993. (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Whacking Weeds for the Elderly, 1991. (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - What's Next Focus Group, 1991. (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Win Fabulous Prizes -- Incentives, 1991-1992. (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Wine Tasting Seminar, 1988. (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Winter Board Meeting, 1990. (Box 132, Folder 3-4)
  - Winter Thaw, 1992. (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Wok Cooking, 1992. (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Woodfest, 1992-1993. (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - World Invitational Rib Championship, 1991. (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - World Invitational Rib Championship, 1991-1992. (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Work Release Subsidy, 1970-1971. (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Write Hanoi, 1971. (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Yellow Feathers at the Polls, 1964. (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Yellow Feather at the Polls, 1968. (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Youth and Sports Activities, 1963-1964. (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Youth and Sports Activities, 1964-1965. (Box 133, Folder 3-5)
  - Youth and Sports, 1965-1966. (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Youth and Sports Activities, 1966-1967. (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Youth Enlists Support through America's Christmas Train and Truck, 1965. (Box 133, Folder 8)
- Photographs, 1975-1997.
  This series consists mostly of extra photograph taken for inclusion in project files. The photographs detail many of the group's activities such as meetings, socials, Beach Music Festival and other events.
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Beach Music Festival, 1988. (Box 134, Folder 4-6)
  - Beach Music Festival, 1988. (Box 135, Folder 1)